





Software engineer

## WHO AM I?

I am a software developer with more than three years of experience who started his career with a passion for GNU/Linux and later fell in love with typings in duck typing languages.

I worked on data-oriented applications with Python, Django, React, etc.

I have experience in the education and finance industry and I am very enthusiastic about startups.

## **SKILS**

- Git
- Python
- Diango
- Gitlab-CI
- GCP
- AWS
- OAuth
- Docker
- LPIC-2

- Javascript
- Typescript
- React
- Redux
- React-native
- Next.js
- MUI
- Storybook

## **EXPERIENCE**

8/2020 - now

### Co-founder & CTO - Full-time

Remotion.live - Paris / France

We pivoted to build an Integrated Assessments system to manage online exams in one place. Remotion I-Assess

- Benchmarking the available Webrtc APIs and applications
- Designing and devloping applications.
- Designing and Developing a pythonic SSO based on open-id connect.
- Integrating SSO with other businesses.
- Leading developers and interns.

python / djnago / flask / tensorflow / typescript / react / tensorflow / next-js / gcp /

# 8/2020 - 11/2020 Software engineer - Part-time

We were trying to start remotion with the Idea of analysing the emotions in the live meetings. Find

- Developing a zero version of the application using GCP Vision API
- Developing Remotion Analyse to process live emotions in the clients browser.
- Later We redesigned the application for end-to-end meetings Radious.

typescript / react / tensorflow-js / cra / gcp-vision-api /

# 8/2020 - 11/2020 Software engineer - Part-time

AVID Arvand - Tehran / Iran

AvidArvand is an international software development company with over 30 years of experience creating content-based platforms and services.

- Customising Keycloak's (SSO) front-end with react-js and new UI.
- Developing a new app based on OCR which helped the company increase the speed of manufacturing.
- Leading new developers.

python / djnago / typescript / react /

### 4/2020 - 8/2020 Software engineer - Full-time

Developing a new microservice for the Knito suite, which was responsible for socialization in the application.

- Benchmarking the technologies to find the best fit for the service.
- Participating in designing the service architecture and database schema.
- Developing the application based on approved designs.

kubernetes / docker / nodejs / postgreSQL / nest-js / GraphQL / redis /

### 6/2019 - 4/2020 Fullstack Python developer - Full-time

I was the maintainer of KNITO studio, a part of Knito Digital Book Store. knito.com

- Adding multi-tenancy support to the STUDIO
- Adding interactive elements to the EPUB
- Integrating the application with SSO and other microservices.
- Developing new features such as Referencing inside the epub, advanced features for HTML Table, etc.
- Configuring CI/CD of the application
- Debugging the old code

kubernetes / docker / django / postgreSQL / redis / drone / Javascript / react / celery / aws /

# **EDUCATION**

2014 - 2019 **Bachelor's Degree** 

**University of Tehran** 

Information Technology engineering

Thesis: Intro to DevOps, and comparing container-based virtualization and serverless Activities and societies:

- Assistant for database course 2019
- Member of IT Association 2015 2017

# LANGUAGES

HOBBIES

English - Working proficiency French - A1

Persian - Native

I love running, biking and building simpler life using new technologies

I trade in stock markets in my free time.